bitofgame.com 2019-06-27

# Privacy - Bit of Game - Free Online Games and MMO's

**General policy.**

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, BitofGame.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes Internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
BitofGame.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk, generally to quickly identify a user’s computer and to “remember” things about the user’s visit, such as your preferences or a user name and password. The Service sends cookies to your computer when you access or view content of Bit of Game. Information contained in a cookie may be linked to your Personal Information for purposes such as improving the quality of our Service, tailoring recommendations to your interests, and making the Service easier to use. You can disable cookies at any time, although you may not be able to access or use features of the Service.

We may feature advertisements served by third party advertising companies which deliver cookies to your computer so the ads you see can be tracked. Since the third party advertising companies tag your computer with a number, they will be able to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement. These advertisers may use Non-Personal Information about your visits to our Service in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We will not provide these third party advertising companies with any Personal Information.

For example, we have contracted with certain companies to place tool bars and advertisements on our applications for cross-promotion purposes. These companies may monitor certain pages of our Service for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement “click-thrus,” and/or other activities on our Service. They use monitoring technologies to compile statistics about our Service visitors.

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy**  
The Service is not geared toward children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information we will delete such information from our files.

**Links to third party Ads**  
From time to time we may include at the Site links to other websites as a service to you. The third party sites are operated by companies that are outside of our control, and your activities at those sites will be governed by the policies and practices of those third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of these third parties before disclosing any personally identifiable information, as we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites.

We allow third party advertisers to post advertisements on our Site. These third parties may place cookies on certain pages of our Site. We do not control those third parties, or their cookies. This privacy policy does not cover those third party advertisers use of cookies.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at submit@bitofgame.biz.

**Third Party Tools/Analytics on Bit of Game**

BitofGame.com also contain third party tracking tools from third party service providers, which may enable these third parties to analyze our Customers’ information. While these third parties may have access to your personal information in connection with the performance of services for BitofGame.com, they will not be permitted to use such information for any purpose other than providing their services.

Our Site includes social media features, such as the Facebook, Twitter and Google+. These features may collect information such as your IP address and which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly or to tailor or personalize the services of the company providing the feature. Social media features are hosted by the third parties who provide such features, widgets or buttons, and your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
• Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on BitofGame.com  
• Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.  
• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  
ADinPlay  
GTBurst  
Ad4Game  
CPMStar

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on BitofGame.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. BitofGame.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
